本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： Ellie 蒹葭子 Yatamisaki RJ王 中二豆奶 LYP 洛一心
校对： 好战青蛙  后期： 小滔
一段时间以来 假冒中央调查局的劫掠
Since some time, some raids conducted by fake CBI
受到中央调查局的关注
has come up before CBI enquiry.
如遇可疑情况 请拨打该号码
Call us on this phone number for any doubtful situation.
您好 长官
Hello, sir.
你为什么想加入调查局?
Why do you want to join the bureau?
什么?
What, sir?
中央调查局 你为什么想加入?
Intelligence. CBI. Why do you want to join it?
我国存在很多腐败问题
There's a lot of corruption in our country.
体制一片混乱
The entire system's in a mess.
潜伏于体制的敌人在苏醒
Our enemies are weakening our system.
我们需要根除敌人 长官
We need to uproot the enemies, sir.
你会根除他们?
Will you uproot them?
我们一起 长官
We'll do it together, sir.
你们和我
You and me.
26个特殊劫匪
共和日
Republic Day.
"共和"这个词 在字典里
"Republic" is a word, which, if you look up its meaning
意思是 一群人被领导着
you see a the picture of a group of people
遵守规定
which guides them to follow rules.
这种共和也称作民主
The same republic is called democracy as well.
印度的共和
The journey of India's Republic.
始于37年前 1950年1月26日
began 37 years ago, with 21 cannon salute
在21响礼炮声中 拉金德拉 普拉萨德博士
and with Dr.Rajendra Prasad hoisting
升起印度国旗
the Indian flag on 26th January, 1950.
宣布印度共和国的历史性诞生
and announced the historical birth of the Republic of India.
四名初级警员 一名女警
Four junior constables and one lady constable
- 再加上你就够了 - 是的
along with you will be adequate. - Yes.
我们要搜查哪里?
Where are we conducting the raid?
我都还不知道
Even I don't know that yet.
只有沙玛先生知道
Only Mr. Sharma knows for now.
十五分钟后在萨福丁庄见面
Meet us at Safdurjung in 15 minutes.
阿杰
Ajay.
先生 我们要迟到了
Sir, we're getting late.
先生 不用紧张
Sir, don't be tense.
要我带队吗?
Do you want me to lead?
你因为他是部长而紧张吗?
Are you nervous because he's a minister?
部长没有国家重要
Ministers are not more important than the country.
你给警察打电话了?
Did you call the police?
打了
Yes, I did.
他们十五分钟后到萨福丁庄
They will be at Safdurjung in 15 minutes.
- 谁是副警长? - 兰维尔 辛格
- Who is the SI? - Ranveer Singh.
我的警棍呢?
Where is my staff?
先生
Sir.
你鞋带松了
Your shoelace is untied.
部长家?
The minister's home?
走吧
Let's go.
8%不算多
8% is not too much.
你的工作不轻松
Your job's not too easy.
部长同意了 否则
The minister's said yes, otherwise
先生 我们是中央调查局的
Sir, we're from the CBI.
我们需要搜查你的房子
We need to search your house.
就算你们是中央调查局的 也不能这样闯进来
So what if you're the CBI, you cannot barge in like this
先生 他们是中央调查局的
Sir. They're the CBI.
我觉得他们想搜查房子
l think they're here to raid your house.
- 阿杰 - 是
- Ajay. - Sir.
- 开始 - 是 长官
- Start.- Yes, sir.
- 你去那边 - 兰维尔
-You look that way. - Ranveer.
你去那边
And you look that way.
长官
Sir.
如果有人耍小聪明 就赏他一巴掌
lf anyone tries to act smart, don't hesitate to slap them.
是
Sir.
过来 快点
Come on, hurry up.
过来 每个人都进来
Come on. Everyone, get inside.
快点
Hurry up.
- 放下电话 - 我
- Keep the phone down. - I
放下 过来
Keep it down. Come on.
都不许出来
No one will come out.
宝贝快吃这甜点
Guddu's going to eat this hot sweetmeat.
张嘴
Eat it.
很好
Bravo.
再吃一口
One more.
像这样
Like this
你是谁?
Who are you?
你不能闯进来
You can't barge in here.
中央调查局搜查你家
The CBI has raided your house.
先生
Sir.
听着 相信我 这里什么都没有
Listen. Believe me, there's nothing in here.
把橱柜钥匙交出来
Handover the cupboard keys.
钥匙丢了 没有了
The key's lost, I don't have it.
少来 交出钥匙
Stop joking, handover the keys.
孩子他爸 你也不管管
Guddu's father, why don't you say something?
他为什么要钥匙?
Why is he asking for the keys?
喊他也没用
No point in calling him.
- 钥匙交出来 - 怎么了?
- Handover the keys. - What happened?
长官 她不肯把橱柜钥匙给我
Sir, she's not handing over the cupboard keys.
我没有怎么给
l don't have it, so how can I
- 砸开锁 - 是
- Break the lock. - Yes.
站一边 别妨碍他工作
Move aside, let him do his job.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
住手
Stop.
他把锁砸坏了
He's broken the lock.
神啊
Oh God.
长官 部长的薪金
Sir. The minister's salary.
看他从橱柜里找到什么了
Look at what they found from the cupboard.
孩子他爸
Guddu's father.
你都没跟我说过这个
You never told me about these.
珊蒂
Shanti.
是
Sir.
这里什么都没有
There's nothing here.
这是奉神的地方
The Lord's resting here.
不要惊扰神
Don't trouble Him.
这里什么都没有
There's nothing.
- 至少顾及神 - 长官
- At least think about the Lord. - Sir.
你要干嘛 你会被诅咒的
What are you doing? You'll be cursed.
过来 神是全知 他不会介意的
Come on. The Lord's omniscient One. He won't say a thing.
- 他会诅咒你们 - 女士 请站旁边
- He'll curse you. - Madam, please step aside.
长官
Sir.
你们太恶毒
You're so mean.
安静
Quiet.
长官 这也是
Sir. This too.
- 等等 - 都拿走
- Stop. - Take all this out.
- 等等 - 等一下
- Stop. - Just a minute.
放手 放手
Leave me. Leave me.
这是他的辛苦钱 不要拿走
lt's his hard earned money, don't take it away.
看 你要扯坏我的衣服了
Look, you're ruining my clothes.
- 松手 - 孩子他爸 快阻止他们
- Let go. - Guddu's father. Stop them.
- 快放手 - 快松开他的毛衣
- Let go. - Come on, let go of his sweater.
你该满足了 他还留着你身上的首饰
You should be thankful that you still have the jewellery you're wearing.
你们会被诅咒的
You'll be cursed.
我们完蛋了
We're ruined.
阿杰
Ajay.
长官 这些文件
Sir, these are the documents.
看这里 长官
Look here, sir.
土地投资合同
These are land investments.
长官
Sir.
- 在这签字 - 这里
- Sign here. - Here.
我有笔
I've one.
借一步说话 长官
Can we step aside for a minute, sir?
长官 我的私人助理很无礼
Sir, my PA's really ill-mannered.
他不懂得与像您这样的
He doesn't have the etiquettes
高级官员谈话的礼节
of how to talk to an officer of your calibre.
他简直是疯子
He's completely insane.
- 我的意思是 - 你打算给多少?
- I was saying, sir. - What's your offer?
你想要多少?
How much do you want?
两份?
Two?
我就得这就差不多
l think that will be fine.
- 两份? - 是的
- Two? - Yes.
P.k. 沙玛
P.K. Sharma.
记住这个名字
Don't forget the name.
告诉你的腐败同僚
And tell your other corrupt friends
祈祷中央调查局不搜查他们家
to pray that the CBI don't raid their homes.
如果他们祈祷了 Pk 沙玛就不去了
And if they do, then PK Sharma isn't conducting it.
先生
Sir.
幸好你只想给他两份
Thankfully, you offered him only two.
- 乔京德尔 - 是
- Joginder. - Sir.
做一份基本资料 列出收缴清单
Lodge an FLR, make an inventory..
- 然后给这边发报告 - 是
- and report back here. - Yes.
让兰维尔 辛格在Gmd上签字
Take Ranveer Singh's signature on the GMD
- 三十分钟内搞定 - 是 长官
- you have only 30 minutes left. - Yes, sir.
- 兰维尔 辛格 - 长官
- Ranveer Singh. - Sir.
无线电通知警察局
Inform your police station over the wireless..
- 乔京德尔会带着这些东西去 - 是
- that Joginder's arriving with all these valuables. - Sir.
你待在这里
You will wait here.
乔京德尔会做一份基本资料再来找你
Joginder will lodge an FLR and come back to you..
- 然后让你在Gmd上签字 - Gmd?
- and take your signature on the GMD and.. - GMD?
有什么问题?
What's wrong?
- 长官 我 - 长官?
- Sir, I - Sir?
Gmd是什么?
What's GMD?
这是你第一次参加搜查?
Is this your first raid?
是 长官
Yes, sir.
你觉得怎么样?
How do you feel?
很好 长官 我成为您的粉丝了
Very good, sir. l've become your fan.
我第一次见到正直的力量
First time I'm seeing the power of honesty.
人就该这样
Such people should be
永远记住 兰维尔 辛格
Always remember one thing Ranveer Singh.
真正的力量源自内心
True power comes from the heart.
永生铭记
Always remember this in life.
好的 长官
Okay, sir.
- 长官 现在我们 - 好
- Sir, now we. - Yes.
- 把车启动 行吗 - 是
- Go and start the car. Okay. - Yes.
- 长官 - 祝你好运 你做的很好
- Sir. - Good luck. Well done.
- 胜利属于印度 - 胜利属于印度
- Jai Hind. - Jai Hind.
你知道吗 长官
You know what, sir.
什么事 珊蒂
Yes, Shanti.
他们真正地尽职尽责
They're doing the real duty.
我们只是
We're just
真正的力量源于内心
True power comes from the heart.
我还能怎么办
What else could I do?
我不知道怎么办
I didn't know what to do.
那个部长还盯着我 打了两巴掌都没用
That minister was still tailing me even after I slapped him twice.
我很害怕
l was so scared.
那个私人助理到没什么 但是
The PA was fine, but then
大家都在干什么
And what was everyone up to?
伊克巴尔无缘无故给我拍照
Iqbal was taking my pictures, without a reason.
是你想要带队
You wanted to lead.
那你就得接着带
Go ahead and lead.
快点
Hurry up.
快 快
Come on, come on.
- 给你 - 好的 兄弟
- Here you go. - Yes, brother.
快走吧
Now leave.
去机场
Airport.
- 老德里车站 - 上车
- Old Delhi Station. - Sit.
先生 从这能买票乘大巴去斋普尔吗
Hey mister, will I get a bus to Jaipur from here?
可以
Yes.
到了
Here you go.
一张去昌迪加尔的票
One for Chandigarh.
再说一遍
Say that again.
珊蒂  他们
Shanti, they
你知道了 长官
You know, sir.
我就知道有点不对
l knew something was wrong.
- 在这等着 - 是
- Wait here. - Yes.
部长先生
Mr. Minister.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我才是完蛋的那个
l've been ruined.
你这么难过干什么?
Why do you look so sad?
我们犯了个小错
We made a small mistake.
-早上好 乔京德尔兄弟 - 早上好
- Good morning, brother Joginder. - Morning.
报纸上有报道吗
Anything in the papers?
没有
Nothing.
印度语报 英语报 旁遮普语报 都没有
Hindi, English, Punjabi, nothing in either of them.
东西全卖了
Sell everything.
我们婚礼见
We'll meet at the marriage.
当然
Of course.
抬高点
Raise that higher.
稍等
Just a minute.
- 新闻上有报道了吗 - 没有
- Anything in the news? - No.
婚礼准备得怎么样了?
How are the marriage preparations?
要忙疯了
I'm going crazy?
女儿的婚礼可比我当年的婚礼
My own marriage preparations were lot smoother
麻烦多了
than my daughter's.
很正常
That's normal.
老爸通常为女儿的婚礼殚智竭虑
The father's normally at his tethers on his daughter's marriage.
还好
That's fine.
你什么时候来?
When are you arriving?
星期五
Friday.
早点来 我挺孤单
Come soon. I feel alone.
需要我带什么吗
Do you need anything?
不用 人过来就行
No, just come here.
带七八箱进口烟
Get me 7 8 cartons of imported cigarette.
给观礼的客人
For the wedding guests.
等等
And wait a minute.
这写的是什么
What's written here?
给新郎一块好表
A nice watch for the groom.
还有呢?
And?
飞利浦录像机
And a Philips VCR.
螺纹梳刀磨床是什么?
And what's a Chaser grinder?
我也不懂
l don't get it.
一双精美的巴塔黑色无系带鞋
A nice black pair of Bata shoes, without laces.
别忘了
Don't forget.
香水和香料
Perfumes and scents.
其他的你看着带吧
And you get anything else that you like.
- 需要车吗? - 不用 我在这订了一辆
- How about a car? - No, l've booked one here.
告诉我你的航班号
Inform me about your flight.
我让人接你
I'll send someone to pick you up.
你得带挺多行李
You'll be carrying a lot of luggage.
好
Fine.
再见
See you.
早点来
Come soon.
你往哪儿走?
Where are you going?
谁来做楼下的工作 懒鬼?
Who will finish the work downstairs, lazy bums?
- 你好 - 我是叔叔
- Hello. - lt's your uncle.
还好么 拉胡尔?
How are you, Rahul?
我很好 你呢?
l'm good. How are you?
我挺好的 你爸爸呢?
l am fine. Where's your papa?
他在洗衣服 我去叫他
He's washing the clothes. l'll call him.
爸爸 阿杰叔叔来电话了
Papa. Uncle Ajay's called.
你都说什么了?
What did you say?
我说你在洗衣服 还能说什么?
l said you're washing clothes, what else?
喂
Hello.
- 报纸有报道么? - 没
- Anything in the papers? - No.
你为什么在洗衣服?
Why were you washing clothes?
洗衣服? 没有
Clothes? No.
我的手帕太脏了
My handkerchief was too dirty.
玛尔蒂去看医生了
Malti's gone to see the doctor.
快看啊!
Look at that!
洗衣服时间打电话
Wasting time on the phone.
我让你去泡茶
l asked you to make tea.
你衣服洗完了?
And, did you finish washing the clothes?
这是总部打来的电话
lt's a call from the head-office.
让他们给你加薪啊
Ask them to give you an increment.
连个家仆都雇不起
You can't even afford a servant now.
家里的活儿都得我一个人干
l've to do all the chores at home.
婚礼上见
We'll meet at the marriage.
- 喂喂 - 在呢
- Hello. Hello. - Yes.
阿杰 别告诉别人
Ajay. Don't tell them about this.
为什么?
Why?
他们会笑死我的
They'll tease me to death.
我不会的
l won't.
回头见
See you.
# 你姓甚名谁 #
Who are you?
# 千里姻缘为何牵 #
How are we related?
# 三生红线为何系 #
What's this bond that binds us?
# 有你我无法自已 #
l can't control myself before you.
# 你姓甚名谁 #
Who are you?
# 千里姻缘为何牵 #
How are we related?
傻丫头 你看不见么?
Stupid girl. Can't you see?
奶奶 我走了
Grandma, l'm leaving.
看看你 别跑 听到没?
Say See you. You're not running away, are you?
# 永远不要离开我 #
Don't ever leave me and go away.
# 只当为我 #
For my sake.
# 不论真假 永不分离 #
Always stay with, whether it's true of false.
# 抑或是幻觉 #
Or just an illusion.
# 我努力去拥有你 #
l've tried my best to make you mine.
# 紧握我双手 让所有人知晓 #
Hold my hands so l can let everyone know.
# 你姓甚名谁 #
Who are you?
# 千里姻缘为何牵 #
How are we related?
什么东西?
What is it?
婚礼请柬
Wedding invitation.
她要结婚了
She's getting married.
跟谁?
To whom?
图卡拉姆
Tukaram.
现在?
Now?
什么现在? 新郎惨了
What now? The groom will be ruined.
洗你的摩托车去
Come on, clean the scooter.
快去
Come on, go.
长官 求你了
Sir, please.
多给我点时间...
lf you give me some more time...
我会查清他们的身份的
l will find out who they were.
- 你不投诉么? - 不
- You don't want to file a complaint? - No.
调查怎么样了?
What about the investigation?
听着 警官 我已经一无所有了
Look, ACP. l've already lost everything.
决不能再把消息透漏给媒体
Now this news shouldn't be leaked out to the press.
就这样
That's it.
有任何补救措施 就去做吧
lf you can still do anything, then go ahead.
没有第一手资料 我们无能为力
We cannot do anything without an FlR.
你可以暂停他们的工作
You can suspend these officers.
他们俩个那天跟那帮小偷是一伙的
These two were helping those thieves the other day.
先生 别再说那帮小偷了
Sir, let's stop arguing over those thieves.
我说了 没有第一手资料我们无能为力
Let me tell you, we cannot do anything without an FlR.
你怎么就不明白呢?
Why don't you understand?
我要保留公众形象
l've a public image.
我的政治生涯就完了
it will be the end of my political career.
不要追究了
No. Let it go.
- 兰维尔 辛格 - 长官
- Ranvir Singh. - Sir.
真为你可耻
Shame on you.
我们会帮助强盗土匪么?
Will we help thieves and robbers now?
不会 长官
You're absolutely right, sir.
幸好部长不打算投诉 否则...
The Minister isn't filing a report, otherwise...
但是 部门会对此进行调查
But, there will be a departmental inquiry.
调查结束前...
And, until the inquiry isn't over...
你和珊蒂要接受停职处分
you and Shanti are suspended.
- 明白了么? - 是 长官
- Got it? - Sir.
再见 先生
See you, sir.
这才对嘛 先生
That was the right thing to do, sir.
让他们俩个停职
Suspending those two.
请用 先生
Here, sir.
欢迎 欢迎
Welcome, welcome.
搬走
Lift this up.
走了 老弟
Come, brother.
老弟 你还在这里
Brother, you're still here.
我们走吧
Let's go. Come on.
那边走
That way.
上来
Come on.
老天！
Hail the Lord!
往边上走
Move aside.
让我坐下
Let me sit.
快点
Come on.
你来了
You're here.
近来可好 沙玛?
How are you, Sharma?
愿主保佑你
Bless you.
恭喜恭喜
Congratulations.
拿行李了么?
Did you get the things?
你好 孩子
Hello, son.
拿行李
Get the things.
行李就在那儿 全部拿走
Yes, the luggage's right there. Take all of them.
过来
Come.
- 其他人到了么? - 到了
- Are the others here? - Yes, they are.
- 早上就到了 - 他们在哪儿?
- They arrived in the morning. - Where are they?
在里面
They're inside.
应该正在吃东西
They must be eating.
- 让他们吃吧 - 现在时吃饭时间
- Let them eat. - This is the time for them to eat.
别取笑他们
Don't taunt them.
他来了
He's here.
- 你们继续 - 恭喜恭喜
- Go ahead, eat. - Congratulations.
过来
Come on.
你还没吃呢
You didn't eat anything.
- 你看上去聪明极了 - 其他人在哪儿?
- You're looking really smart. - Where are the others?
给你介绍我的孩子们
l'll introduce you to my kids.
- 这是莎库达 - 你好
- This is Sukhwinder. - Hello.
- 这是柏米达 - 你好
- This is Parminder. - Hello.
- 这是曼宁达- 你好
- This is Maninder. - Hello.
- 这是吉特达- 你好
- This is Jitender. - Hello.
- 这是哈米达- 你好
- This is Harminder. - Hello.
- 这是达哈米达 - 你好
- This is Dharmender. - Hello.
- 她要结婚了 婷基 - 你好
- She's getting married, Tinky. - Hello.
这是沙玛夫人 - 你好
- And she's Mrs. Sharma. - Hello.
这是阿杰 伊克巴尔 乔京德尔
And this is Ajay, lqbal, Joginder.
她才刚出生
And she's newly born.
还没起名字
We haven't given her a name yet.
就这些
That's it.
我们没有电视
We didn't have television.
大惊喜
Surprising.
照张相
Take a picture.
# 抓紧时间 不然... #
Hurry up, or else...
# 月亮就要升起 #
The moon will rise up.
# 帐篷将 #
The tent will be...
# 充满雾气 #
Filled with fog.
# 我愿沐浴在你的芳泽 #
l want to bathe in your colour.
# 你是如此美丽 #
You are so beautiful.
# 你是如此珍贵 #
You look priceless.
# 每次见到你 #
Every time l look at you.
# 心脏停止跳动 #
My heart skips a beat.
# 你的脸庞 #
Your face...
# 未束的长发遮住你脸庞 #
Your face covered with tresses.
# 如此迷人 #
lt's so awesome, girl.
# 未束的长发遮住你脸庞 #
Your face covered with tresses.
# 如此迷人 #
lt's so awesome, girl.
# 朋友们说 #
My friends say.
# 男人只知道调情 #
Boys are such a flirt.
# 朋友们说 #
My friends say.
# 男人只知道调情 #
Boys are such a flirt.
# 对女孩永远甜言蜜语 #
They always sweet-talk girls.
# 我挚爱的人啊 #
Beloved.
# 如果你也是其中之一 #
lf you're one of them.
# 如果你伤了我的心 #
lf you break my heart.
# 我该怎么办? #
Then what about me?
# 我挚爱的人啊 #
Beloved.
# 任你万般试探 我都不会背叛 #
l'm no betrayer, test me all you want.
# 只愿与我共度一晚 #
Just spend a night with me.
# 我发誓永不离开 #
l will never leave you, l swear.
# 此爱到永远 #
l will love you all my life.
# 我是影子 你是太阳 我的挚爱 #
l am the shadow, you are the sun, beloved.
# 你是无价之宝 我的挚爱 #
You are priceless, beloved.
# 每次见到你 #
Every time l look at you.
# 心脏停止跳动 #
My heart skips a beat.
# 你的脸庞 #
Your face...
# 未束的长发遮住你脸庞 #
Your face covered with tresses.
# 如此迷人 #
lt's so awesome, girl.
# 爱情游戏 #
The game of love.
# 满是谎言 #
ls a deceitful one.
# 爱情游戏 #
The game of love.
# 满是谎言 #
ls a deceitful one.
# 自由岌岌可危 #
Your freedoms always at stake.
# 我挚爱的人啊 #
Beloved.
# 你将不可自拔 #
You can't get out of it.
# 我不想爱上任何人 #
l don't want fall in love ever.
# 我挚爱的人啊 #
Beloved.
# 爱我 信我 惟愿一次 #
Love me, trust me just once.
# 我将永伴左右 #
l will always be with you.
# 用你真心... #
lf you give me your heart...
# 换我所有 这是我的承诺 #
l will give you everything, that's my promise.
# 我们是天作之合 #
We're made for each other.
# 你是无价之宝 亲爱的 #
You are precious, beloved.
# 每次见到你 #
Every time l look at you.
# 心脏停止跳动 #
My heart skips a beat.
# 你的脸庞 #
Your face...
# 未束的长发遮住你脸庞 #
Your face covered with tresses.
# 如此迷人 #
lt's so awesome, girl.
你参加婚礼是对的
You did the right thing by attending the marriage.
玩得多开心
We had such fun.
你都打电话了我怎么能不来?
How can I not come if you call?
- 印度万岁 - 长官
- Jai Hind. - sir.
印度万岁
Jai Hind.
还有其他事么 授库拉纳 先生?
Anything else, Mr. Khurana?
- 你可以走了 我们一会儿谈 - 是
- You can leave, l'll talk to you later. - Yes.
授库拉纳 先生?
Mr. Khurana?
是的 他们认为我是警局情报员
Yes. They think l'm the IG of police.
往远了想 雏鸟已变雄鹰
Think big. The children have grown up.
与以往大不相同 越来越吓人了
lt's not like before. lt's getting scarier.
昨晚做了个梦...
Last night l had a dream, that...
我女婿来监狱看我
my son-in-law's come to see me in jail.
而你不见了
And you were nowhere to be seen.
你没仔细看
You didn't look properly.
我肯定站在你身后
l must be standing right behind you.
下一站去哪里?
Where's the next one?
加尔各答
Kolkata.
加尔各答哪里?
Where in Kolkata?
巴达大巴扎
Bada Bazaar.
那里好么?
ls it good?
什么时候?
When?
一周之后
A week later.
- 大事还是小事 - 小事
- Big or small. - Small.
想想干些大事
Think something big.
干大事需要人手...
We'll need more people do something big...
还有钱
and that means more money.
要不是干这个 这个年纪我早退休了
Had l been doing a job, then l would've retired at this age.
五年前你就这么说
You've been saying that for the last 5 years.
我现在是认真的
No, l'm serious now.
三年前你也这么说
You've been saying that for the past 3 years.
拿着
Here you go.
里面有机票和现金
The tickets and money are in this.
你 乔京德尔和伊克巴尔直接来见我
You, Joginder and lqbal will meet me directly.
- 没问题吧? - 没问题
- Okay? - Okay.
再见
See you.
- 保重 - 没问题
- Take care. - Yes.
快跑 快跑 快跑 快跑 快跑
Run, run, run, run, run.
停车 停车 停车
Stop, stop, stop.
停车
Stop.
- 抱歉 - 上来
- Sorry. - Come on.
- 你好 哈曼 - 你好
- Hi, Aman. - Hi.
过来
Come on.
- 我们走 - 再见
- Let's go. - Bye.
- 再见 爸爸 - 再见
- Bye, dad. - Bye.
- 父亲 叫我父亲 - 再见 父亲
- Father. Call me father. - Bye, father.
- 我们差点没赶上公车 - 拉胡尔的电话
- We were about to miss the bus. - Rahul's called.
你的纱巾呢?
Where's your veil?
你好 拉胡尔
Yes, Rahul.
哪里?
Where?
我马上就到
l'll be right there.
有急事 我去去就回
Something urgent has come up. l'll be back soon.
就这样子去?
Will you go like this?
是的 没问题
Yes, it's okay.
早上好 长官
Morning, sir.
你确定是他么?
Are you sure it's him?
是的 长官 他一会儿就到
Yes, sir. He'll be here soon.
- 谁能认出他来? - 穆纳 长官
- Who will identify him? - Munna, sir.
别打我 别打我 让我走吧
Don't beat me. Don't beat me, sir. Let me go.
我还有孩子要养
I've children.
闭嘴 否则我更要揍你了
Shut up or we'll beat you more.
放了我吧 让我走
Leave me. Let me go.
你怎么把他打成这样了?
Why did you beat him so much?
他们跟你比起来还算温柔的 瓦萨姆长官
They were gentle compared to you, Waseem sir.
走
Move.
古普塔长官
Sir. Gupta.
- 是他吗? - 是的
- Is that him? - Yes.
无赖 过来 看看是不是他
Rascal. Come here. Identify him.
是的 就是他
Yes, that's him.
- 快去 - 是 - 快
- Go. - Sir. - Come on.
嘿 古普塔 别动
Hey. Hey, Gupta. Stop.
过来
Come here.
站住
Stop.
你要去哪? 快把车停下
Where are you going? Stop the car.
站住
Stop.
停下来
站住
Stop.
让开
Hey, move.
你...
You...
停下
Stop. Stop.
停车
Stop.
怎么了?
Hey, what is it?
我是中央调查局的 跟上那辆人力车
CBI. Follow that rickshaw.
靠近
Closer.
你走吧
Run. You..
你想死吗?
Do you want to die?
别过来
Don't come any closer.
我会跳下去的
I will jump down.
别再过来了
Don't come any closer.
待在那 我会跳下去的
Stay there. I will jump down.
别动
Stay there.
我说了别动
I say stop.
长官 他这才交做实事
Sir. He's doing the real job.
我们就...
We're just...
走开
Step aside. Move.
这边 先生
Come, sir.
- 早上好 老师 - 早上好
- Good morning, teacher. - Morning.
你好吗?
How are you?
别跟我说话
Don't you dare talk to me.
你去哪了?
Where were you?
昌迪加尔
Chandigarh.
我朋友的女儿结婚了
My friend's daughter was getting married.
我本来想改天见你的 但是那个老东西...
I tried to meet you the other day, but the old man...
- 我父亲 - 是的 就是他
- Father. - Yes, him.
整个晚上我都在打你电话...
I tried calling you all evening...
但是每次都是他接的
but he answered the call every time.
你看见请柬了吗?
Did you see the card?
怎么样?
How was it?
为什么要浪费你爸爸的存款呢?
Why are you wasting your father's provident fund?
奶奶非常喜欢这个男孩
Grandma really likes the boy.
你好像很高兴
You look happy.
你真的那么喜欢图卡拉姆吗?
Do you like that Tukaram as well?
我高兴因为我知道...
I'm happy because I know...
你不会让我嫁给图卡拉姆
you won't let me marry that Tukaram.
再者 你到底在等什么?
By the way, what are you waiting for?
一笔大买卖
For a big tender.
你把你的骗局和偷盗称为大买卖
You call your scams and thefts tender.
我还有一些耻辱感
I still have some shame left in me.
为什么这种事情对你这么重要呢?
Then why do such things in the first place?
因为我只会做这个
Because that's the only thing I know.
人们都浮躁不安...
People are restless..
而我的想法也变得飘忽不定
and my mind is restless.
无论何时我一看见你...
Whenever I look at you...
就会重获新生
I feel like being good.
这就是你要逃避我的原因吗?
Is that why you keep running away from me?
我试过了 但是没办法
I try, but I can't.
婚礼就在下周了 阿杰
The marriage is next week, Ajay.
我知道
I know.
如果你被抓了怎么办?
What if you're caught?
这世界上没人能抓住我
There's no one in this world who can catch me.
- 印度万岁 长官 - 印度万岁
- Jai Hind, sir. - Jai Hind.
- 早上好 长官 - 早上好 长官
- And look, sir. - Good morning, sir.
在坎普尔有个类似的案子
A similar case took place in Kanpur.
- 一年前 - 我找找 这个
- A year ago. - I see. This one.
早上好 长官
Good morning, sir.
长官
Sir.
- 印度万岁 - 印度万岁
- Jai Hind. - Jai Hind.
你听说了一月二十六号的案子吗?
Did you hear about the 26th January case?
是的
Yes.
四个假装成我们部门的人组织了一次突击搜查
Four people conducted a raid posing as officers of our department.
因为种种原因部长没有报案
The minister isn't filing a case for obvious reasons.
- 因为他的名声 - 是的
- For reasons best known to him. - Yes.
为了维护自己的名声...
The minister isn't filing a case...
部长没有报案
for reasons best known to him.
这是个很简单的案子 长官
It's a simple police case, sir.
- 你得知道他... - 可是 先生
- You do know that they... - But still, sir.
为什么完全不追究...
Why indulge in such petty...
你看见那个人了吗?
Do you see that man?
他叫Sl 就是他助了那帮人一臂之力
He's the Sl who helped them conduct the raid.
真可怜 他很羞愧
Poor guy, he was humiliated.
他管理一个学术研究...
He conducted an investigation...
并且收集有关的信息
and gathered this information.
这两年里有十三起这样的案子
There have been 13 such cases in the last 2 years.
只有一部分被调查了
These are the ones that were detected.
没人知道具体数字
No one knows the real number of cases.
假装中央调查局 税务局或者Acb
Fake CBI, Income Tax or ACB teams
搞一次突击搜查...
conduct a raid...
受害者从来不上报
and the victims never report.
谣言满天飞
Rumours are spreading.
有些人总结认为罪犯是前任中央调查局
There's a theory that they're ex-CBI.
很奇怪
Strange.
算了 我们得制止这些谣言
Anyway, we've to stop this nonsense.
他们正在诋毁我们的名声
They're slandering our name.
马德拉斯 那格浦尔 特里凡得琅 勒克瑙
Madras, Nagpur, Trivandrum. Lucknow.
长官 这些地方遍布了整个国家
Sir, it's all over the country.
他们的目标大多数是商人和政客
They mostly target businessmen and politicians.
因为他们有很多黑钱...
Because there's black money involved...
没人希望报道这个
no one wants to report it.
这些政客都来自哪些党派 长官?
Which party do these politicians belong to, sir?
每个党派都有
They're from every party we know.
我希望你尽快解决这件麻烦事
I expect you to end this nuisance immediately.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
长官 我还从来没升职和加薪过
Sir, I haven't received a promotion and increment yet.
家里都快揭不开锅了
It's getting difficult to run the household.
我应该开始收受贿赂了吗?
Shall I start accepting bribes?
你又在威胁我
Threatening me again.
我们就事论事
I'm discussing this matter.
站在我的角度想想
Consider it done from my side.
- 印度万岁 长官 - 印度万岁
- Jai Hind, sir. - Jai Hind.
这起案子里的四个人...
And in that case all the four officers...
- 他们办成了税务员 - 这 看看这个
- they posed as income tax officers. - Here, take this.
- 早上好 长官 - 早上好
- Good morning, sir. - Good morning.
他是瓦萨姆长官
He's Waseem sir.
他将接手这个案子
He will be handling the case.
我是Sl 伊克巴尔 乔京德尔 印度万岁
Sl Ranveer Singh. Jai Hind.
- 为什么他总站着? 坐下吧 - 坐
- Why is he standing? Let him sit. - Sit.
- 我没事 - 不 坐下
- No, I'm fine. - No, sit.
- 不 我... - 请坐
- No, I... - Please. Please.
- 坐下 - 坐下
- Sit. - Sit.
坐
Sit.
他们骗了你 兰维尔先生
They made a fool of you, Mr. Ranveer.
是的
Yes.
你能准确的告诉我发生了什么吗?
Will you tell me what exactly happened?
那是一月二十六号
It was the 26th of January.
我正在值班
I was on duty.
接到了个电话
I received a call.
'这里是图格鲁克路警察局 你好'
'Tughlak Road police station, hello.'
'印度万岁'
'Jai Hind.'
- '印度万岁' - '你是谁?'
- 'Jai Hind.’ - 'Who's this?'
'Sl 伊克巴尔 乔京德尔'
'Sl Ranveer Singh.'
'我是中央调查局十六号探员阿杰乔京德尔’
'This is Ajay Singh from CBI ward 16.'
'从属于Pk 沙玛主任的办公室'
'From additional director PK Sharma's office.'
- '今天谁值班?' - 是我 长官
- 'Who is the officer on duty?' - 'That's me, sir.'
'我们需要一些人 进行一次突击搜查'
'We need some men, to conduct a raid.'
'多少人 长官?'
'How many, sir?'
'四个年轻的警察 一个女警外加你'
'Four junior constables, and one lady constable along with you.'
- '那就够了' - '在哪?'
- 'That will be enough.' - Where's the raid?'
'我们都还不知道'
'Even we don't know that.'
'只有沙玛先生知道'
'Only Mr. Sharma knows.'
'十五分钟后在萨福丁庄和我们集合'
'Meet us at Safdurjung in 15 minutes.'
- '印度万岁' - '印度万岁'
- 'Jai Hind’. - 'Jai Hind.'
- 一共四个人 - 是的 长官
- Four of them. - Yes, sir.
然后呢?
Then?
然后...
Then...
'你不能闯进这...'
'You just can't barge in here...'
'别碰那电话'
'Keep the phone down.'
'相信我 这里什么都没有'
'Believe me, there's nothing in here.'
'女士 请走开'
'Madam, please step aside.'
'古都 爸爸 让他们停下'
'Guddu's papa, stop them.
'让他走'
'Let go of him.'
兰维尔 辛格 有没有人告诉你或者你...
Ranveer Singh, did someone tell you or did you...
如果换做是你的话那么...
If you had been in my place then...
如果是我的话这件事决不会发生
If I had been in your place this situation would've never come up.
我不会和中央调查局一起搅这摊浑水!
I didn't join the CBl to screw up!
我承认是我的错 瓦萨姆长官
l admit my mistake, Waseem sir.
我没必要听你的奚落
I don't have to listen to your taunts.
我来是因为我需要你的帮助
I came here because l needed your help.
如果我们联手就能迅速的解决这个案子
If you help me we can solve this case quickly.
否则 别误会 我已经知道错了
Otherwise, don't be mistaken that I've admitted defeat.
我会花很长的时间独自反省...
It will take me longer alone...
但是 不解决这件事情我是不会罢休的
but, I won't rest until I don't put an end to this.
这才是我想听的
That's what l wanted to hear.
- 联系一下所有的警察局 - 是 长官
- Co-ordinate with all the police stations. - Yes, sir.
伊克巴尔 你得检查所有的违法记录...
And Ranveer, you will check all the police records yourself...
因为你是唯一见过他们的人
because you're the only one who have seen them.
是 长官
Sir.
希望能找到他们的违法记录
Let's hope we find their police records.
什么时候能见到部长?
When can we meet the minister?
什么事?
Yes. What is it?
长官 这是瓦萨姆 卡恩
Sir, this is Waseem Khan.
是中央调查局
From CBI.
还来?
Again?
这次是真的
He's the real one.
你好
Hello.
出租车
Taxi.
巴达 巴扎
Bada Bazaar.
- 乔京德尔 - 长官
- Joginder. - Sir.
阿杰
Ajay.
别浪费我的时间
Don't waste my time.
否则我会记下来的
Otherwise i'll note this down.
- 记下来 - 是 长官
- Note this down. - Yes, sir.
- 你是? - 中央调查局 你呢?
- You? - CBI. And you?
- 什么... - 税务局
- What... - Income Tax Department.
沙玛先生 给我那张纸
Mr. Sharma, give me the papers.
沙玛先生 那张命令书 快点
Mr. Sharma, the order papers. Quick.
你是阿革瓦交易员 ?
Aggarwal Traders?
我是波达交易员
Poddar Traders.
- 这是124号房? - 214!
- 124? - 214!
怎么搞的?
What's this?
你怎么弄混了?
Why do you mess up?
你看清楚了数字吗?
Can't you see the numbers properly?
你会害我丢掉工作的
You'll make me lose my job.
越老越不中用
You've grown old.
我们应该去124...
We were supposed to go to 124...
结果你带我们来214
instead you brought us to 214.
- 看见了吗? - 对不起 长官
- See? - Sorry, sir.
对不起!
Sorry!
- 你真该退休了 - 对对
- It's time for you to retire. - Yes.
有时候是这样 事情被下属搞砸 没事的
It happens sometimes. Things mess up. It's ok.
对不起 这是一个误会
Sorry, it was a slight blunder.
你继续
You can continue.
你继续你的工作 我们回去干我们的
You can get on with your job, and we'll get back to ours.
- 走吧 - 是
- Let's go. - Yes.
阿革瓦交易员
Aggarwal Traders.
我们来自税务局
We're from the Income Tax.
没人允许你们这么做 没人
No calls allowed. None.
- 长官... - 安静点
- Sir... - Quiet.
- 长官 这儿什么都没有 - 钥匙在哪?
- Sir, there's nothing. - Where's the key?
- 钥匙在哪? - 长官... - 拿着
- Where's the key? - Sir... - Get it.
长官 这账本...
Sir, the accounts...
长官 你做了些什么?
Sir, what have you done?
- 我告诉过你找不到东西的 - 闭嘴
- I told you won't find anything. - Shut up.
- 过来 - 长官 长官...
- Come on. - Sir, sir...
你只是在撕床垫而已
You're tearing the mattress.
- 剩下的钱在哪? - 长官...
- Where's the rest of the cash? - Sir...
- 在哪? - 长官 求你了
- Where is it? - Sir, please.
- 钱在哪? - 伊克巴尔
- Where's the money? - Iqbal.
钱在哪...
Where's the cash...
把这个床垫挪开 快点
Move this mattress. Hurry up.
往后 扶住我
Move back. Hold me.
怎么了?
What's going on?
把他们赶走 全部赶走
Clear them out. Clear all them out.
这发生了什么?
What's going on here?
- 在这签名 - 长官 长官求你了
- Sign here. - Sir, sir please.
长官 我们做个交易怎么样
Sir, can't we reach some compromise.
- 长官 求你了 - 要我逮捕你吗?
- Sir, please. - Shall I arrest you?
我们怎么离开这?
How will get out of here?
你怎么就不明白
Why don't you understand?
不是这些 我是说在地下室的那些东西
Not these. I'm talking about the ones in the vault.
好的 先生
Right, sir.
我知道 我见过这些
I know. I've seen these.
- 兄弟 - 怎么了
- Brother. - Yes.
我需要点帮助
I need a little help.
- 兄弟 - 没什么 这是我的职责
- Brother. - No, no. It's okay. It's my duty.
- 非常感谢你 - 谢谢
- Thank you very much. - Thank you.
喂
Hello.
是的
Yes.
是的 班纳吉先生 你好吗?
Yes, Mr. Banerjee. How are you?
什么时候?
When?
哪?
Where?
几个人?
How many people?
一手资料?
FIR?
不 班纳吉先生 不管是否报道...
No, Mr. Banerjee. Whether anyone reports this or not...
我希望这则新闻能被播出去
I want this news to be reported.
明天的报纸上必须见到这则新闻
This has to get printed in tomorrow's newspapers.
我不管
l don't care.
印刷必须要夺人眼球
lt has to be printed big and bold.
好吗? 谢谢
Alright? Thank you.
晚安
Goodnight.
- 有发现吗? - 没有 长官
- Find anything? - Nothing, sir.
加尔各答, 巴达 巴扎
Kolkata, Bada Bazaar.
一只四人所得税造假组织发动了一次突然袭击
A fake income tax team of four conducted a raid.
那些商人都不愿报道此事
No business man wants to report this.
但它依然会刊登在明天的报纸上
But it will still be in tomorrow's newspapers.
给这些流氓点颜色看看
Let's make these rascals nervous.
恭喜
Congratulations.
所得税造假...
Bogus lncome Tax...
四人被捕...
Four people came dressed...
阿杰
Ajay.
- 加内普 - 长官
- Janp. - Sir.
长官
Sir.
找到他了
Found him.
- 你确定? - 百分百是他
- Are you sure? - 100% .
他说他叫P.k. 沙玛...
He said his name was P.K. Sharma...
我永远也忘不了一件事
and l can never forget one thing.
"永远不要忘记 兰维尔 辛格.
"Always remember, Ranveer Singh.
真正的力量源于内心
Real power comes from the heart.
永远听从心的指挥."
Always listen to your heart."
就是他 长官
lt's definitely him, sir.
我们上报纸了
They've published about us.
这写的很清楚 四个人假扮...
lt's clearly written here Four people posed as...
阿杰 现在怎么办?
Ajay, what now?
沙玛先生 你过去总是说...
Mr. Sharma, you always said...
...干一起大的 再退休
...Let's do something big, and then retire.
你想好去哪儿了?
Do you have something in mind?
- 哪里? - 孟买
- Where? - Mumbai.
这值得吗?
ls it worth it?
你要更加卖力工作
You'll have to work harder.
日子可能有点苦 但回报很丰厚
lt might be painful, but the amount is huge.
时机合适吗?
ls this the right time?
因为 现在人人都知道
Because, now everyone knows
有人在假扮中央调查局
there's something called a fake CBl.
现在正是时候
This is the best time.
我会再联系你的
l'll call you later.
好好照顾自己
Look after yourself.
- 地址是哪儿? -  昌迪加尔
- What's the address? - Chandigarh.
我能去抓他吗?
Shall l get him?
那之后你打算怎么办?
And what will you do after that?
关起来 审讯他
Lock him up, interrogate him.
第二天他就会被释放
He'll be released the next day.
没人愿意指证他
No one will testify against him.
- 向他问好 - 是的 长官
- Say hello to him. - Yes, sir.
什么?
What?
录下他的电话
Tape his calls.
# 即使上帝亦或整个世界抛弃了我 #
Even if Lord or this world forsakes me
# 即使我的身体亦或灵魂欺骗了我 #
Even if my body or my soul deceives me.
# 但我的挚爱 我们的爱情... #
But my beloved, the love between us...
# 让我们的爱情永存于世 #
Let the love between us stay forever
# 我们的爱情... #
The love between us...
- 你什么时候到的? - 昨天
- When did you arrive? - Yesterday.
我们现在就要走吗? 但是我的行李
We're leaving now? But my luggage.
- 不 不是今天 - 怎么是出租车?
- No, not today. - Why a taxi?
你的车呢?
Where's your car?
我卖了
l sold it.
让他安静点
Make him quiet.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello. - Hello.
我是电话局的
l'm from the telephone exchange.
- 225463是您的号码吗? - 是的
- 225463? - Yes.
请问您通话时有干扰吗?
ls there a disturbance in the line?
没有
No.
那么为什么要投诉呢?
Then why lodge a complaint.
我们没有啊
But we didn't.
真是225463?
225463?
是我的号码
That's my number.
那一定是您的家人投诉的
Then someone else from your family must have.
让我看看电话吧
Show me your phone.
进来吧
Come.
就是这个
Here's the phone.
有轻微干扰
There's a slight disturbance.
- 我什么也没听到 - 您说什么呢?
- l don't hear a thing. - What are you saying?
难道听不到呜晟吗?
Don't you hear a 'Whoosh' sound?
什么都听不到
l don't hear anything.
电话那头情况会更糟
lt's worse for the caller on the other side.
你看啊
l'll show you.
这两条线不能碰到
These two wires shouldn't touch each other.
碰到就会有呜甑纳音了
lf they do, then you hear that 'Whoosh' sound.
你难道都不清理的吗?
Don't you clean it?
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
人们总是不爱清理自己的电话机
People don't clean their telephone sets
到头来这活儿还是我们的
and we're burdened with all the work.
你看 这样清理后
You see, the circumference can be cleaned
里里外外焕然一新
from inside as well as outside.
我们再检查下
Let's check.
你好 先生
Hello, sir.
- 你好 - 这里是225463
- Hello. - 225463.
一切正常吗?
All okay, sir?
是的
Yes, all okay.
有干扰吗?
Any disturbance?
顾米特 赶紧挂了电话出来
Gurmeet, disconnect the call and get out.
好的 先生
Fine, sir.
大功告成
That's done.
你什么时候离开?
When are you leaving again?
今天晚上
Today evening.
那什么时候再回来?
And when will you return?
不会回来了
Never.
为什么?
Why?
因为很快当地警方就会开始找我
Because soon the local police will be looking for me.
很重要的事吗?
ls it important?
最后一次了
Last time.
如果这次出事了怎么办?
And what if something happens this time?
不要吓我
Don't scare me.
我们直接在星期四见
We'll meet directly on Thursday now.
机场 四点整
4 o'clock, in the airport.
阿杰 我现在就愿意和你远走高飞
Ajay, l'm willing to leave with you right now.
- 非要冒这个险吗? - 普丽娅 ..
- Do you have to take this risk? - Priya...
你怎么就不明白呢?
Why don't you understand?
如果出了什么差错呢?
What if something goes wrong?
- 不会出事的 - 万一呢?
- Nothing will happen - What if something does?
- 什么也不会发生的 普丽娅 - 阿杰
- Nothing will happen, Priya - Ajay.
如果你出了什么事 我...
lf anything happens to you, l...
要我把你留下吗?
Shall l leave you home?
你还能给我什么?
How much more will you leave me?
# 你是如此 永存我心 #
# Just you... you dwell in my heart.
# 如同眼中 氤氲梦境 #
# Just like dreams... in my eyes.
# 没有你 泪水模糊视线 #
# Without you... my eyes brim with tears.
# 没有你 我亦不复存在 #
# Without you... l don't exist either #
# 你是我生命的全部 #
# You mean everything to me #
# 你是如此 永存我心 #
# Just you... you dwell in my heart #
# 如同眼中 氤氲梦境 #
# Just like dreams... in my eyes #
# 爱 只拾取盈盈一把 #
# Love... picks only a handful few #
# 却给了人间梦与忧愁 #
# Gives them dreams, and sorrows #
# 顷刻之间 美梦破灭 #
# Shatters all their dreams in a minute #
# 爱人之心 随之凋零 #
# lt can ruin one #
# 没有你 泪水模糊视线 #
# Without you... my eyes brim with tears #
# 没有你 我亦不复存在 #
# Without you... l don't exist either #
# 你是我生命的全部 #
# You mean everything to me #
# 你是如此 永存我心 #
# Just you... you dwell in my heart #
# 如同眼中 氤氲梦境 #
# Just like dreams... in my eyes #
# 姐妹 姐妹 #
# Sister... Sister... #
# 爱如旅程 人生苦短 #
# The journey that's love... is a short one #
# 恋人总是 风雨共济 #
# But lovers... are always treading on this path #
# 爱之旅途 漫漫无际 #
# The path of love is a never-ending one #
# 爱情本身 永垂不朽 #
# lt's undying #
# 没有你 泪水模糊视线 #
# Without you... my eyes brim with tears #
# 没有你 我亦不复存在 #
# Without you... l don't exist either #
# 你是我生命的全部 #
# You mean everything to me #
# 你是如此 永存我心 #
# Just you... you dwell in my heart #
# 如同眼中 氤氲梦境 #
# Just like dreams... in my eyes #
操作员 0172225463
Operator, 0172225463.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello. - Hello.
是的 昂儒
Yes, Ajju.
拿到票了吗?
Did you get the tickets?
拿到了
Yes, l did.
跟乔京德尔和伊克巴尔说过了吗?
Did you talk to Joginder and lqbal?
说过了
Yes, l did.
他们会在德里机场和你碰头
They will meet you at Delhi Airport.
我知道了
l see.
怎么了? 你听上去不太好
What's wrong? You sound worried.
没事 累了而已
Nothing, just tired.
你现在不可以疲倦
You're not allowed to tire right now.
最后这票做完 你就能退休享福了
Once we do this last job, you can retire for good.
明天机场见 晚安
See you tomorrow at the airport. Goodnight.
晚安 孩子
Goodnight, son.
跟乔京德尔和伊克巴尔说过了吗?
Did you talk to Joginder and lqbal?
最后这票做完 你就能退休享福了
Once we do this last job, you can retire for good.
你好 迪帕克
Yes, Deepak.
沙玛最后一通电话从哪打来的?
Where did Sharma get the last call from?
孟买 海洋城堡酒店
Bombay, Sea Castle.
房间号呢?
Room no?
长官 沙玛接到一个叫昂儒的从孟买打来的电话
Sir, Sharma received a call from some Ajju from Bombay.
昂儒现在在海洋城堡酒店1453房
Ajju's staying in Sea Castle, room no. 1453.
长官 沙玛他们明天要在
Sir, Sharma will be meeting
德里机场和叫乔京德尔和伊克巴尔的人会合
some Joginder and lqbal at Delhi airport tomorrow.
他们今晚就要离开孟买
And they will leave for Bombay in the evening.
昂儒会去孟买机场接他们
Ajju will pick them up from Bombay airport.
长官 他们提到了什么最后一票
Sir, they were mentioning something about a last job.
派人跟上沙玛
Send someone after Sharma.
我要知道他从昌迪加尔到那里的一举一动
l want details of his every movement from Chandigarh to here.
打给孟买警局的索朗奇
Call Solanki at Bombay office...
长官 索朗奇已经调走了
Sir, Solanki's been transferred.
谁接替他的?
Who's been appointed in his place?
索朗奇 长官
Solanki, sir.
让他获取关于昂儒的一切信息
Tell him to get all the information on Ajju's.
再订三张明天去孟买的票
And book three tickets for tomorrow for Bombay.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
再放一遍
Show me this one again.
我很快就回来
l'll be back soon.
- 好的 - 别担心
- Yes. - Don't worry.
- 关好卧室的门闩 - 好的
- Fix the bedroom latch. - Yes.
- 照顾好他 - 好的
- And look after him. Okay. - Yes.
好的 再见
See you. Okay.
就是那三个
That's the three.
抱歉 借下电话
Excuse me. Phone please.
他们说吉亚尼 达亚尔 辛格不是总统
They say Gyaani Dayal Singh isn't President
拉吉夫 甘地才是
it's Rajiv Gandhi.
是的
Yes.
给
Here.
二十卢比
20 rupees.
谢谢
Thank you.
刚才离开的那个人 让你登什么广告?
That man who just left, what ad did he give you to publish?
这个
This one.
跟上前面的出租车 快点
Follow that taxi. Come on.
- 你好 - 谢谢
- Hello. - Thank you.
- 长官 - 印度万岁
- Sir. - Jai Hind.
盯住刚才进去的人
You've to keep an eye on the people that just went inside.
长官 这是我们的队伍
Sir, this is our team and
这次行动我们一起完成
they will be working with us on this team.
好的 从昂儒开始
Okay, let's start from Ajju.
从昨天起他一直用A. K 瓦德汉的名字
Sir, he's been staying in Hotel Sea Castel
入住在海洋城堡酒店
since yesterday under the name of A. K Wardhan.
他在登记处留下了特里凡得琅的地址
He's given a address of Trivandrum in the register.
我查过了 长官
l checked it out, sir.
地址是伪造的
That address was a fake.
今早他离开酒店去了杰哈里市场
Sir, today morning he left the hotel and went to 'Jhari Mandi'.
那里是造假知名地
lt's a notoriously famous place known for forgery.
从那里他又去了班德拉的一家广告公司
Sir, from there he went to a local ad booking agency in Bandra.
订了明早登这个广告
He's booked this ad for tomorrow.
招聘五十名优秀毕业生
Wanted 50 dynamic graduates
担任情报人员和安...
for intelligence officer's post and secoo...
- 是安检 - 是 是安检人员
- Security. - Yes, security officer's post.
男士或女士请单独来访
Males and females come personally
面试请携带履历表 资格证书
for interview with bio-data, certificates
护照标准照 时间1987年3月18日
passport size photo on 18th March, 1987
地点 海洋城堡酒店
at Hotel Sea Castle.
来电咨询时间 上午十点至下午五点
Enquiry counter between 10 am and 5 pm.
- 这是什么... - 非常重要 昂儒
- What's this... - This is really big, Ajju.
因为这是最后一次
Because it's the last one.
但要这么多人干什么?
But why do you need so many people?
因为是大工程
Because it's a big job.
估计需要别人的帮助
Consider that we'll need public support.
他们在谋划大事
They're planning something big.
昂儒还去哪了?
Where else did Ajju go?
离开班德拉就去了机场
From Bandra he went to the airport.
接了那三个人就回了酒店
He picked up the three and then hotel.
- 索朗奇 - 长官
- Solanki. - Sir.
我们需要新据点 离酒店越近越好
We need a new base. The closer to their hotel, the better.
是
Yes.
我要十到十二个人去参加他们的面试
l need 10-12 people for their interview.
找能力强的人去
Give me some really smart men
要能通过他们的面试
who can crack their interview.
让我们看看他们想搞什么花样
Let's find out what they exactly want.
长官
Sir.
为何不直接去问沙玛?
Why not go ask Sharma directly?
伊克巴尔 我知道你为什么急着想见沙玛
Ranveer, l know why you're in a hurry to meet Sharma
但是 按我的方式来
But, use my mind as well.
你明白吗?
Do you get that?
长官
Sir.
地址是?
The place?
卜虎万 达斯 辛哈尼亚珠宝
Bhuvan Das Singhania Jewels.
歌剧院
Opera House.
- 你太伟大了 - 你太伟大了
- You're great. - You're great.
别激动 冷静 - 你太伟大了
Calm down. Calm down. - You're great.
冷静
Calm down.
你太棒了
You're great.
孩子他妈!
Mother!
你整天要做的除了吃就是睡
All you do is eat and sleep the entire day.
一动不动
You don't move a muscle.
看这个广告 读读
Look at this ad. Read it.
好好干
Do well.
别怕
Don't be afraid.
你要去哪儿啊儿子?
Where are you going, son?
去... 去... 去...
ln... in... in...
好吧 我知道了
Okay, l get it.
好 那么 各位注意 行动
Okay, then. Alert everyone. Move.
好 下一个
Okay. Next.
阿奇莱 乔杜里- 是的 长官
Akhilesh Chaudhary. - Yes, sir.
谁让你坐下了? - 对不起 长官
Did anyone ask you to sit down? - Sorry, sir.
出去
Out.
什么?
What?
出去!
Out!
卡皮尔 古卡长官
Kapil Gorkar, sir.
桑杰 莫 长官 - 拉吉夫 古普特
Sanjay More, sir. - Rajiv Gupte.
- 理查 辛格 长官 - 阿尼杰钱德拉
- Richa Singh, sir. - Anuj Chandra.
大声点
Speak louder.
阿尼杰 钱德拉!
Anuj Chandra!
基申 乔杜里 长官
Kishen Chaudhary, sir.
姓名卡米尼
Name, Kamini.
年龄 二十一
Age, 21.
三围 36-28-36
Vital stats, 36-28-36.
你...- 坐下 坐下
You... - Sit, sit.
你可以坐下
You please sit.
你为什么要加入我们部门呢?
Why do you want to join the bureau?
我们国家有太多贪污腐败现象
There's a lot of corruption in our country.
我们的敌人正在削弱我们的组织
Our enemies are weakening our system.
我们需要铲除敌人 长官！
We need to uproot the enemies, sir.
你要铲除他们吗?
Will you uproot them?
我们要共同完成 长官
We'll do it together, sir.
你们...和我
You... and me.
我们就是贪污行为的终结者 长官
We've to put an end to corruption, sir.
我想为国家做贡献 长官
l want to do something for the country, sir.
因为 我天生聪明
Because, l'm born intelligent, sir.
我想铲除所有的偷盗行为
l want to eradicate all the thieves.
长...
Si...
中央调查局的全称是什么?
What's the full form of CBl?
印度中央银行
Central Bank of lndia.
中央调查局
Central Bureau of lnvestigation.
中...
Ce...
印度中央银行 长官
Central Bank of lndia, sir.
中央调查局
Central Bureau of lnvestigation.
普拉桑特 帕萨卡
Prashant Pathak.
阿维尼 塞斯长官 - 塞琴 恩卡 长官
Avinash Seth, sir. - Sachin Goenka, sir.
苏迪普 查特基 - 阿伦 卡库德卡
Sir, Sudeep Chatterjee. - Sir, Arun Kakodkar.
普拉卡什 马达夫 长官
Prakash Madhav, sir.
你在这之前还做过什么工作
Where else have you worked prior to this?
我是个作家 长官 我需要陈述什么吗?
l'm a writer, sir. Shall l narrate something?
你会开车吗?
Do you know how to drive a car?
我为汽车驾驶座而生
l was born on the driver's seat.
看见什么人了么?
Did you see anyone?
没有 长官
No, sir.
你为什么觉得你是这份工作的最佳人选?
Why do you think you're the right person for the job?
长官 我... - 请讲英语
Sir, l... - Please answer in English.
因为我诚实  长官
Because l am honest, sir.
因为我有一颗要为国家奉献的心
Because l want to do something to my country.
我爱我的祖国
l love my country.
我要为国奉献
l want to do... my country.
我诚实守纪 长官
l am honest and disciplined, sir.
我很勤奋 长官
l am hardworking, sir.
我还是个小孩子的时候 我就想为祖国做贡献
Even when l was a small kid, l wanted to do my country.
我职业道德高尚
And l've good work ethics.
大家都想成为电影明星 板球队员...
People's wanted to be film-stars,cricketers...
但是我只想在情报机关工作
...but l always wanted to be intelligence.
在外边等着
Wait outside.
面试的结果将在下午五点公布
The results of this interview will be announced at 5pm.
- 努尔 阿巴斯 -到 长官
- Noor Abbas. - Yes, sir.
- 尼汀 潘德 - 到 长官
- Nitin Pande. - Yes, sir.
- 阿伦 卡库德卡 - 到 长官
- Arun Kakodkar. - Yes, sir.
- 普拉卡什 亚达夫 - 长官
- Prakash Yadav. - Sir.
阿维尼 塞斯- 到 长官...
Avinash Seth. - Yes, sir...
冉迪亚 布拉库帕 - 到 长官
Randir Belapurkar. - Yes, sir.
桑杰 莫 - 到 长官
Sanjay More. - Yes, sir.
米尼玛 简- 到 长官
Minal Jain. - Yes, sir.
加丹 达莫德尔
Jagan Damodar.
你好
Hello.
是
Yes.
好 好的
Fine. Okay.
长官 是莱恩
Sir, it was Rane.
莫和古普特被选上了
More and Gupte have been selected.
恭喜 长官
Congratulations, sir.
还有 基申 乔杜里
And, Kishen Chaudhary.
长官
Sir.
恭喜 你们所有人
Congratulations, all of you.
谢谢长官
Thanks, sir.
很遗憾...你们可以离开了 谢谢
But, l am sorry... all of you can leave. Thank you.
他们选错了人
They've chosen the wrong people.
热烈祝贺
Many, many congratulations.
我的名字是 A.k. 瓦德汉
My name is A.K. Wardhan.
你们是二十六人特别小组
You are Special 26.
你们是最聪明智慧的
You've proven to be the smartest, intelligent...
也是最棒的
...and the best.
但是我们的筛选并没有结束
But our selection process isn't over yet.
明天...
Tomorrow...
立正  站直!
Stand straight. Straight!
明天早上十一点 你们在这里报到
Tomorrow morning at 11 am you will all report here.
短发 工装
Short hair, and formally dressed.
罗伊和舒克拉先生会给你们上课
Mr. Roy and Mr. Shukla, will give a lecture.
这个课大概持续两个小时
This class will last two hours.
午饭后 你们会有一个最终考试
Post-lunch you will have a final exam...
我们称之为实践
...which we call practical.
实践中 你们将组成中央调查局中的一支队伍
ln the practical, you'll be a part of our CBl team...
进行一场突击检查
...that will conduct a raid.
分配给你们的任务
The whole idea of putting you guys in this situation...
就是为了核实你是否能化解压力
...is to verify if you can handle pressure or not.
或者说 是考察你们是否
Or let me correct myself, whether you can handle...
能够化解极限的压力
...extreme pressure or not.
嘿 别害怕 放轻松
Hey. Don't be scared, get it.
- 是 长官 - 很好
Yes, sir. - Good.
泰米尔? - 到 长官
Tamil? - Yes, sir.
中央调查局不是微风 是海啸
CBl is not just wind, its Tsunami...
不管是谁
Whoever it maybe, Whoosh.
好了 让我们席卷而去!
That's all. We will sweep him up!
长官 你说一遍 就犹如说了数百遍!
Boss. When you say it once, it's like saying it a hundred times!
非常好
Good.
帕特尔- 到 长官
Patel. - Yes, sir.
努力工作
Do your job with hard work...
让违法分子一想到我们就出冷汗
...that law-breakers start sweating thinking about us.
好的 长官
Yes, sir.
我们是四个人 他们是二十二个
There's 4 of you and 22 of them.
这不是歧视
This isn't discrimination.
你们四个人也能做二十二个人的事
4 of you can do what these 22 can.
我信任你们 - 谢谢 长官
l believe and trust you. - Thank you, sir.
记住一件事
Remember one thing.
真正的力量是源自内心
Real power comes from the heart.
在人生中不要害怕任何人
Don't ever be scared of anyone in life.
明白吗? - 明白 长官
Understood? - Yes, sir.
完成突袭任务之后
After the completion of the raid...
你们要回到这里报到 如果没有任何差错的话
...you will all report back here, and if nothing goes wrong...
你们每人都能得到自己的委任书
...everyone will get their appointment letter.
然后 你们可以开一个小派对
And then, you can all throw a small party for all.
好的 长官
Sure, sir.
女士们先生们 你们刚刚开始了自己
Ladies and Gentlemen, you're just one step away from...
步入印度最优秀智慧的部门的第一步
...becoming a part of lndia's best and intellectual agency.
中央调查局意味着你爱的祖国及一切
CBl means, that you love your country above everything else.
中央调查局意味着你为你的国家而生
CBl means, that you will live for your country...
为国家而死
...and that you will die for your country.
中央调查局意味着你就是最棒的
CBl means, that you're the best.
你们是不是最棒的? - 是 长官
Are you the best? - Yes, sir.
我听不见 - 是 长官!
l can't hear you. - Yes, sir!
我还是听不见 - 是 长官!
l still can't hear you. - Yes, sir!
现在的会议内容不能外泄
These discussions shouldn't leave this room.
明白吗? - 是 长官!
Do you understand? - Yes, sir!
解散
Dismiss.
谢谢长官
Thank you, sir.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
真不错
Great.
这一刻我几乎忘了我们是贼了
For a minute l forgot that we're thieves.
他们问我们中央调查局的全称
They asked us the full form of CBl.
甚至最喜欢的歌
They even asked me my favourite song.
而且还说让我们明天上午十一点
They've asked us to report at the conference room...
去会议室报到 进行培训
...tomorrow at 11 am, for some lecture.
他们说我们午饭后会有一次外出的突击检查
They said we'll go out for a raid post-lunch.
在哪呢? - 他们还没说呢
Where? - They haven't said that yet.
还有吗?- 他们说祝贺我们 我是最棒的
Anything else? - They said Congratulations, l'm the best.
他说我是最棒的 长官
He said l am the best, sir.
好的
Fine.
你明天要去报到
You can go and report their tomorrow.
保持高度警惕 - 是 长官!
Be sharp and alert. - Sir!
再见 - 再见 好梦
See you. - Bye. Goodnight
晚安 - 晚安- 晚安 - 晚安
Goodnight. - Goodnight. - Goodnight. - Goodnight.
- 好梦 - 晚安
- Sleep well. - Goodnight.
你是谁?
Who is it?
你是谁? - 客房服务 先生
Who is it? - Room service, sir.
# 我梦中的女王 你何时会降临 #
The queen of my dreams, when will you come.
# 生命转瞬即逝 你会在何时降临 #
Life is passing by, when will you come?
进来
Come in.
你还好吗 沙玛先生?
How are you, Mr. Sharma?
我们是中央调查局的
We're from the CBl.
真正的中央调查局
The real one.
那么 沙玛先生
So, Mr. Sharma.
你喜欢玩官兵抓贼的游戏 对吧?
You like playing cops-and-robbers, don't you?
不 我只是...
No, l was just...
我要问你几个问题 你有两个选择
l will ask you some questions, and you will have two options.
首先 你会否认所有事
Firstly, you will deny everything...
说你什么都不知道
...and say you don't know anything.
在这种情况下
ln that condition,
我们会把你带到一个地方严刑逼供
we'll be compelled to do it and...
绝对会让你印象深刻
...in places, which was never done to you before by anyone.
你将会很痛苦 但是相信我
lt will cause you a lot of pain but, believe me...
你可能会瞬间想起所有细节
...you will suddenly remember everything in detail.
我...我...
l... l...
你的第二个选择就是跟我们合作
Your second option is that you cooperate with us...
这会节省我们很多时间和精力
...and save our time and effort.
而且也不会给你带来任何痛苦
This option won't cause you any pain...
你还可以请求我们的些许宽大处理
...and you can expect us to be slightly lenient with us.
好吧 开始吧
So, let's begin.
第一个问题 你们虚假中央调查局明天要在哪
First question, where's your fake CBl team...
进行突击检查?
...going to conduct a raid tomorrow?
胡万达斯 辛哈尼亚 珠宝店
Bhuvandas Singhania Jewels.
- 几点? - 下午三点
- What time? - 3 pm.
那什么是二十六人特别小组?
What's Special 26?
那是个挺大的地方 所以我们想...
lt... was a big place, so we thought...
需要更多人手
...if we have more men with us...
所以你们在报纸上登了广告
So you put an ad in the paper...
说来一个要一个 照单全包
...stating Come one, come all,
这个是一个大买卖 帮助我们 是不是?
it's a big heist. Help us.
计划是什么?
What's the plan?
明天上午我们会给他们做培训
Tomorrow morning we'll give them training.
培训?
Training?
我的意思是说明他们的分工
l mean we'd explain them their role...
比如 做什么 怎么做
...like what to do, how to do it.
我们要解释给他们 还要准备
We would explain them all that and prepare them.
下午两点半一过 我们的车就到达酒店门口
And then at 2:30, our bus would reach the hotel.
然后呢?
Then?
然后我们就去大剧院
We were supposed to go to Opera House in it...
进行一次突击
...and conduct a big raid.
我们是中央调查局 都别动!
We're from the CBl! No one moves!
现在 开始
Come on, start.
快点 明白吗
Come on, get it.
进去 快点
Get in, quickly.
快点 快点 快点
Come on, come on, quickly.
抓紧时间
Hurry up.
长官 长官 对不起 长官
Sir.. please sir.. sorry sir..
所有都收走
Pick up everything.
我们会在别人反应过来之前逃走
We would flee before anyone knew what happened?
我们计划在三十分钟内抢两千万卢比
We planned to loot 2 crores in 30 minutes.
昂儒是什么背景?
What's your Ajju's background?
他想加入中央调查局
He wanted to join the CBl.
他笔试过了
He had cleared the written exam.
但是面试失败了
But failed in the interview.
考试的失利让他很受伤
He failed in the exam and he was hurt.
所以她开始进行冒充中央调查局
So he started a fake CBl team.
迄今为止你们犯案多少次?
How many raids have you conducted so far?
明天是第五十次
We were supposed to complete half century tomorrow.
那是...
What the...
我要确认一件事
l've to admit one thing.
这是只有你们四个人
There's just four of you...
但是你消息散布混乱
...but you've spread a chaos.
不是四个
Not four.
人们也愿意帮我们
People like him help us as well.
长官 我能跟他单独谈一分钟吗?
Sir, can l talk to him in private for a minute?
干嘛一分钟 你明天可以跟他慢慢谈
Why a minute, you can talk to him all you want tomorrow.
好吧
Yes.
那 告诉我 沙玛先生
So, tell us, Mr. Sharma.
你想要安全还是跟他们一样被抓?
Do you want to be safe or go down with them?
让我告诉你...
Let me tell you...
监狱对于你这个年龄的人来说可不是好地方
...jail isn't a great place for people of your age.
长官 长官 我选另一个
Sir... sir, another option.
我还有孩子要养
l've children.
你在干这个之前想过这个吗
You should've thought that before.
想过...
l did...
快说 我们没时间等你
Tell us. We don't have time.
沙玛先生
Mr. Sharma.
我需要做什么?
What will l have to do?
就像你们计划的那样进行
Just do as you were supposed to.
忘掉我们今晚见过
Forget that we ever met.
所有的事都按原计划进行
Everything should go as it was supposed to.
跟你说吧 我们中的一些官员...
Let me tell you, that a few of our officers...
... 也在你的二十六人特别组里
... are in your Special 26 team.
所以别跟我耍花招
So don't try to act smart.
我要逮捕他们 不是要杀了他们
l want to arrest them, not kill them.
干嘛?
What's wrong?
我就是想起了一些事
l just remembered something.
昂儒总是说没人能抓到他
Ajju always said there's no one who can catch him.
自负让许多人都栽了 沙玛先生
Over-confidence has led to the downfall of many, Mr. Sharma.
昂儒也不例外
Ajju's no different.
你会不会对他很残忍...
Will you treat him too harsh...
别操他的心了还是担心你自己吧
Stop worrying about him and think about yourself.
去休息吧
Get some sleep.
你明天还有事要做
You've a busy day tomorrow.
晚安
Goodnight.
再把情况过一遍
Brief More and Gupte again.
我们明早见
We'll meet tomorrow morning.
- 晚安 - 晚安 长官
- Goodnight. - Goodnight, sir.
- 不好意思 - 没关系
- Sorry. - lt's okay.
先生
Sir.
一杯酒要这么多钱啊?
All that money for one drink?
- 有多少? - 30毫升 先生
- How much? - 30 ml, sir.
- 还有更少的吗? - 没有了 先生
- Anything smaller? - No, sir.
好吧 这个给我来一杯
Fine. Get me this one.
好的 先生
Okay, sir.
你好
Hello.
- 我叫瓦萨姆 - 在下瓦德汉
- Waseem. - Wardhan.
瓦德汉先生 你是做什么的?
What do you do, Mr. Wardhan?
进出口贸易
lmport-export.
打扰了 先生
Excuse me, sir.
先生 您的酒
Sir, your drink.
- 先生 来点苏达? - 我又没点苏达
- Sir, soda? - l didn't ask for soda.
先生 这是附赠的
Sir, it's complimentary.
好吧 倒吧 行了
Go ahead, pour it. That's it.
- 先生 水 - 好
- Sir, water. - Yes.
你做什么的?
What do you do?
在政府工作
Government job.
你说什么?
What are you saying?
在政府工作?
The government works?
- 干杯 - 噢... 干杯
- Cheers. - Oh... Cheers.
你对政府有很多怨言吧
You've a lot of complaints with the government.
就是一些牢骚嘛 瓦萨姆先生
Only the weak complain, Mr. Waseem.
大家都和你一样
And people like you.
像我这样的人只会喝着自己的酒过自己的日子
People like me just have their drink and live their life.
还能有什么?
What else?
你想得开啊
What a thought.
- 服务生 - 先生
- Waiter. - Sir.
- 把酒送到我房间 - 好的 先生
- Put the tab on my room. - Sure, sir.
- 晚安 瓦萨姆先生 - 晚安
- Goodnight, Mr. Waseem. - Goodnight.
- 瓦德汉先生 - 什么事
- Wardhan sir. - Yes.
你的钱掉了
l think you dropped your money.
是你的吗?
ls this yours?
是 是我的
Yes, it's mine.
谢谢
Thank you.
什么态度?
What an attitude?
我一定要亲手抓了他
l will hunt him down personally.
尼汀 斯瑞瓦斯达
Nitin Srivastav.
卡皮尔 顾瑞卡
Kapil Gorekar.
阿琴娜 曼萨卡
Archana Mansekar.
谢谢
Thank you.
米尼玛 简
Minal Jain.
哈瑞史 潘迪卡
Harish Pendekar.
早上好
Good morning.
- 早上好 长官 - 早上好 长官
- Good morning, sir. - Good morning, sir.
海尔 克里希纳!
Hail Krishna!
先生
Sir.
看那边
Look there.
是的 索朗奇先生
Yes, Solanki sir.
玛干达斯 这位是瓦萨姆 卡恩先生
Magandas, this is Mr. Waseem Khan..
- 知道了... - 中央调查局的
- l see.. - From CBI.
中央调查局的?
CBI?
为什么是中央调查局...
Why CBI...
那个
That.
看到了没?
Did you see that?
这就是他们想要的
That's exactly what they bank on.
- 你偷过东西吗? - 没有
- Did you steal anything? - No.
- 抢过吗? - 没有
- Plunder? - No.
那你干嘛那么怕中央调查局?
Then why are you so scared of the CBI?
可是你要倒霉了
Something terrible going to happen with you instead.
- 你的店要被抢了 - 什么?
- Your shop's going to be looted. - What?
什么时候?
When?
三点左右
Around 3 pm.
大概有三十个人会来这里...
Around 30 people will come here...
以中央调查局官员的身份出现然后洗劫你的店
... posing as CBI officers and loot your shop.
你想要避免它发生吗?
Do you want to avert it?
你这是在给我选择的机会吗?
Are you telling me or giving me a choice?
- 你有没有安全屋? - 有
- Do you have a safer place? - Yes.
我的车间
My workshop.
有多远?
How far?
到那边二十分钟
20 minutes from here.
好
Good.
我们要把你店里的珠宝...
We'll replace your store's jewellery...
... 换成假的 - 是
... with your fake jewellery that's marked. - Yes.
在半个小时内把你店里所有的东西...
Shift the entire stock in your shop...
... 都转移到你的车间去
... to your workshop in half an hour.
半小时? 怎么可能 长官?
Half an hour! How is it possible, sir?
当然有可能 先生
lt's possible, sir.
他们会在三十分钟内洗劫你的店
They were going to loot your shop in 30 minutes.
我知道了
l see.
你的员工留在店里就行了
Only your staff will stay in your shop.
- 好的 - 你的店要关门
- Okay. - Your shop will be closed for the public.
有官员会扮成消费者
Some of officers will wait for them posing as customers.
长官 在你知道这些事的时候...
Sir, when you know all this...
... 为什么不逮捕他们?
... why don't you arrest them?
- 先生 - 是
- Sir. - Yes.
不能惩罚那些想犯罪的人
One cannot be punished for thinking of such crimes.
而只能惩罚真正犯罪的人
Only for committing it.
也只有当我们掌握证据时才能这么做
And only if we've evidence.
记住 没有任何权威可以凌驾于你
Remember that, there's no authority over you.
没有什么力量能阻碍你
No one has the power to stop you.
更没有人能阻止你
No one can stop you.
也没人能将你...
And no one has the power to come between you...
... 与你的责任分开
... and your duty.
- 明白吗? - 是的 长官
- Understand? - Yes, sir.
奶奶
Grandma.
我要走了
l am leaving.
这个放那边
Keep this in there.
把这个放在那里
Keep this over there.
- 我打个电话 - 是 长官
- l'll make a call. - Yes, sir.
这个
This one.
- 长官 - 拉胡尔 那边怎么样了?
- Sir. - Rahul, what's going on there?
在训练 长官
Training, sir.
- 没有什么事吧? - 没有 长官
- Anything to worry? - Nothing, sir.
- 索朗奇 - 长官
- Solanki. - Sir.
不好意思 夫人 本店今日暂停营业
No madam, today the shop is closed for customers.
请您明天再来吧
You please come tomorrow.
长官
Sir.
- 那边安排一个狙击手 - 是
- l want a sniper there. - Yes.
派你的人到路两边去
Send few of your men to both the lanes.
两个在角落里两个在那边 穿的普通点
Two on that corner and two on that one, dressed in civil.
好的
Okay.
我们的车要停对地方...
Our vehicle should be stationed...
他们停车的时候 马上就拦下他们
... exactly where they park their bus, to block it.
好的 长官
Okay, sir.
打开
Open it.
快点
Quickly.
- 快点 - 放下来
- Quickly. - Load it.
快 快
Quickly. Quickly.
- 还要多久? - 长官
- How much longer? - Sir.
几分钟就好了
Just a few more minutes.
把首饰放下来去检查一下摄像机
Load the jewels and check the CCTV.
是 长官
Sir.
来
Come.
走
Go.
好了 伙计们
Okay, guys.
现在吃午饭吧
You can have your lunch now.
三十分钟后见
See you in 30 minutes.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, sir.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
紧张吗?
Nervous?
受不了了
Can't handle it anymore.
我已经老了
l've grown old.
这是最后一次了
This is the last one.
好好享受它吧
Enjoy it.
别担心 今天我带队
Don't worry. l'm leading today.
你把他们留在巴士里就行了
You can leave them in the bus.
我跟乔京德尔还有伊克巴尔一起开车去
l will come along with Joginder and lqbal in the car.
好的
Okay.
嗯 拉胡尔
Yes, Rahul.
长官 现在是午饭时间 他们按计划行动
Sir, its lunch-break. They're on schedule.
好的 他们的巴士一离开那里就通知我
Fine, inform me as soon as the bus leaves from there.
知道了 长官
Right, sir.
- 都准备好了吗? - 准备好了 长官
- ls everyone ready? - We're fully ready, sir.
好的
Okay.
摄像机没问题 长官
CCTV's working perfectly, sir.
- 看看货车到哪里了? - 长官
- Find out where has the van reached? - Sir.
放那边
Keep it there.
- 就位 - 是 长官
- Take position. - Yes, sir.
你们明白的
You understand that.
- 罗伊先生 - 是 长官
- Mr. Roy. - Yes, sir.
长官
Sir.
- 巴士的车牌号是Mrt-2431
- The bus's no is MRT-2431.
好的 行动
Okay, out.
大家听好
Listen, everyone.
听着
Listen.
巴士刚才离开酒店了
The bus has just left the hotel.
三十分钟后就会到这里
lt will be here in 30 minutes.
如果谁想上厕所 现在就去
lf anyone wants to use the bathroom, do it now.
听我指挥
Wait for my signal.
不要... 重复一遍
Do not... l repeat,
没有我的指示谁都不能行动
nobody will move until l signal.
- 清楚了吗? - 是 长官
- Right? - Yes, sir.
- 兰维尔 检查外面的情况 - 是 长官
- Ranveer. Check the status outside. - Yes, sir.
- 长官 - 嗯
- Sir. - Yes.
嘿
Hey.
- 你们在干嘛? 各就各位 - 长官
- What are you doing here? Get to your positions. - Sir.
长官 我们在干正事儿
Sir, we're doing the real job.
他们...
They're just...
'你工作这么卖力 肯定也很苦'
'You'll have to work hard, might pain you as well.'
'但是赚的钱也不少啊'
'But the money involved is huge.'
'这个时间好吗?'
'ls the timing right?'
'再没有更好的时间了'
'There can't be a better time.'
左边停下
Stop at the left.
- 基申 - 长官
- Kishen. - Sir.
这是什么?
What's this?
警察总局 长官
Police Headquarters, sir.
基申 我要去核实讨论事项
Kishen, l'll go verify the order papers.
你们到胡万达斯 辛哈尼亚 珠宝店去...
The rest of you get to Bhuvandas Singhania Jewellers...
... 等我还有瓦德汉长官
... and wait for me and Wardhan sir.
我们到那里之前...
No one will get down from the bus...
... 谁都不许下巴士
... as long we get there.
这是命令!
That's an order!
-是的 长官 - 好
- Yes, sir. - Good.
走吧
Let's go.
- 打扰一下 先生 - 是
- Just a minute, sir. - Yes.
麦德龙电影院怎么走?
Sir, which way to Metro Cinema?
直走然后左拐
Go straight and take a left.
谢谢你 先生
Ok sir, thank you.
- 诶 - 你还想要私下谈啊?
- Yes. - So, you wanted to talk to me in private?
你太会装蒜了 看我不打你
You were acting too smart. l'll slap you.
- 好啦 到车里换衣服 - 嗯
- Come on, change your clothes in the jeep. - Yes.
- 珊蒂  - 先生
- Shanti. - Sir.
- 你怎么样? - 还不错
- How are you? - Fine.
路边停下
Stop at the side.
- 深德- 长官
- Shinde. - Sir.
- 不要让任何人进来 - 是长官
- Don't let anyone in. - Yes, sir.
你是谁?
Who are you?
听好了 这是中央调查局查抄
Come on. This is a CBI raid.
所有人放下手里的活儿
Everyone stop working.
快点 别干了
Come on. Stop working.
- 中央调查局查抄 - 别干活了
- lt's a CBI raid. - Stop your work.
- 放下手里的活儿 - 快停下来
- Stop your work. - Stop working.
把文件收起来 我说... 快点
Close that file. l said... Come on.
别干活儿了
l said stop the work.
起来 起来
Get up. Get up.
停下来
Stop your work.
夫人 快点 快点
Madam, come on. Hurry up.
- 这边 - 快点 出去
- This way. - Come on. Get out.
- 别管了 快点 - 快点
- Leave him. Hurry up. - Come on.
查他们的账本
Check their account books.
- 查账本 - 谁都不许碰账本
- Check their account books. - No one will touch the account books.
把账本放下 不要改东西
Keep the account books down. No changes.
我说了不要改... 这里写了什么?
l said no changes... What's written in this?
嘿 把电话放下来
Hey. Keep the phone down?
- 长官 - 里面写了什么?
- Sir. - What's written here?
- 这些条目是什么? - 我不知道 长官
- What are these entries? - l don't know, sir.
这不是我的错
lt's not my mistake.
把账本给我
Give me that account book.
- 这是什么? - 长官 我不知道
- What is this? - Sir, l don't know.
这是什么?
What's this?
你们所有的商品都会被没收的
All your goods can be seized?
- 你知道吗? - 长官 拜托了 长官
- Do you know that? - Sir, please, sir.
- 你没有许可证 - 长官
- You don't have one proper paper. - Sir.
罗伊 没收所有的东西
Roy. Seize everything.
- 可是 长官... -闭嘴!
- But, sir... - Shut up!
老板让我这么做的
Sir asked me to do this.
带你老板去犯罪科 快点
Bring your sir to Crime Branch. Come on.
- 打开保险柜 - 长官 我会丢掉饭碗的
- Open the vault door. Come on. - Sir, l will lose my job.
- 打开就好 - 长官
- Good that you do. - Sir.
打开 快点
Open it, quickly.
快 你们两个 出去
Come on. You two, out. Out.
- 你没有权利进去 - 长官
- You haven't got a single proper entry in this register. - Sir.
- 跟我来... - 听我说...
- Come with me... - Listen to me...
这里面写了什么?
What's written here?
这是什么?
What's this?
这个放进去
Keep this inside.
拿上这个
This one too.
别太贪婪
Greed is not good.
放下那个
Keep that out.
那个也放下
That one too.
那个拿上
Keep that one.
对 那个也拿上
Yes, that one too.
在这里签上你的大名
Sign here. Write your name here. Name.
快点
Come on, hurry up.
好  谢谢
Yes, thank you.
小心 快点
Careful. Hurry up.
- 跟上 赶紧 - 放在那儿
- Quickly, quickly. - Yes, there.
赶紧
Quickly.
- 赶快 - 快
- Hurry up. - Fast.
- 这是你的份额 - 多给点吧 长官
- Here's your share. - Madam, a little more.
- 走开 - 我干得很卖力
- Get lost. - I worked so hard.
我真想揍你 你演过火了
I will break your face. You were over-acting.
我也因为扮演路人甲而少分了钱
I was paid less for the ACP's role as well.
- 我也少分了钱 - 滚开
- I'm being paid less here too. - Get lost.
保重
Take care.
我们很快就再见
We'll meet again soon.
- 再见 - 再见
- See you. - Soon.
过来
Come here.
你...
You...
中央调查局!
CBI!
天啊!
Oh God!
是来突击查抄的吗?
Here to conduct a raid?
别说话!
Quiet!
你想查抄的话 请便
If you're here to conduct a raid, then go ahead.
你在里头干啥?
What are you doing inside?
等上司回来
Waiting for the boss.
上司在哪?
Where's the boss?
在来的路上
He's on the way.
滚开
Get lost.
赶紧
Hurry up.
还有多久
How much longer.
知道了
Got it.
你好
Hello.
我是
Yes.
什么?
What?
你说什么?
What are you saying?
先生
Sir.
长官
先生 中央调查局查抄了玛干达斯的车间
Sir, the CBI raided Magandas's workshop.
- 什么 - 报告长官
- What? - Yes, sir.
我们刚接到电话
We just received a call.
- 中央调查局做的? - 是的 长官
- CBI? - Yes, sir.
- 查抄车间? - 是的 长官
- The workshop? - Yes, sir.
他曾被羞辱
He was humiliated.
他展开调查
He conducted an investigation...
并收集信息
... and gathered this information.
为什么他站着? 让他坐下
Why is he standing? Let him sit.
- 不用了 长官 我站着好了 - 坐下吧
- No, sir. I am fine. - Come on.
伊克巴尔 他们都低估了你
They made a fool of you, Ranveer.
我来这是因为我需要你的帮助
I came here because I needed your help.
有你的帮助 这件案子会更快解决
If you help me, this case will be solved faster.
我必须承认一点
I'll have to admit one thing.
这儿只有你们四人 但你却制造了混乱
There are just four of you, but you've spread chaos.
不是四个
Not four.
别人也会帮我们
People like them help us as well.
多美好啊
How wonderful.
试想一下
Just remembered.
昂儒常说 没有人能抓住他
Ajju always used to say,there's no one who can catch him.
索朗奇 过来
Solanki, come here.
- 是的 长官 - 我们队伍有多少人?
- Yes, sir. - How many people in our team?
长官  加上你我 拉胡尔和伊克巴尔约27
Sir, counting you, me, Rahul and Ranveer around 27.
索朗奇 蓝威尔不是警察
Ranveer isn't a police officer, Solanki.
兰尼是昂儒的助手
Ranveer was Ajju's aide...
派来我们部门做间谍警察
...who came to our office posing as a police officer.
而我们都这么信任他
And we believed him.
- 印度万岁 - 他是谁?
- Jai Hind. - Who's this?'
蓝威尔 珊蒂 他们都是间谍
Ranveer, Shanti, they are all fake.
你和四个警察
You, along with four junior constables...
加上一个女警察就够了
...and one female constable will be enough.
我们15分钟后在萨福丁庄见
We'll meet at Safdurjung in 15 minutes.
他们都在那儿
They were all in this.
他们... 他们都是间谍!
They... they are all fake!
- 你确定? - 百分百肯定
- Are you sure? - 100% .
我们都不知道我们在为他们服务
We didn't know, but we were playing for their team.
索朗奇 我们是二十六人特别组
We're Special 26, Solanki.
这群流氓不仅抢劫商铺
The rascals didn't just rob the shop...
还抢劫工厂
...but also the workshop.
索朗奇
Solanki.
在 长官
Yes, sir.
我在哪能找到一些水?
Where can I find a handful of water?
啥? 长官
What, sir?
水
Water.
一些水
Handful of water.
# 天涯海角 觅我踪迹 #
You'll find me everywhere I go, I know that.
# 自我发觉 我心属你 #
I now belong to you, since I know, that's your influence.
# 日渐接近 探究你情 #
I close to you, in your feelings.
# 入你记忆 #
In your memories.
# 永存我心 #
Now you dwell in me.
# 你姓甚名谁 #
Who are you?
# 千里姻缘为何牵 #
How are we related?
# 三生红线为何系 #
What's this bond that binds us?
# 有你我无法自已 #
I can't control myself before you.
# 你姓甚名谁 #
Who are you?
# 千里姻缘为何牵 #
How are we related?
我们到了 停车 停车 停车
We're here. Stop, stop, stop.
公交到了
The bus is here.
- 谢谢 - 来吧 孩子
- Thank you. - Come, son.
十分感谢
Thank you. Very good.
- 再见 - 走吧
- Bye. - Let's go.
- 爸爸再见 - 再见
- Bye, dad. - Go.
瓦萨姆先生
Waseem sir.
你有一张汇票
There's a money-order for you.
汇票? 哪的汇票?
Money-order? From where?
来自比哈尔区博杰普尔的拉卡米普
Laxmipur, Bhojpur, District Bihar.
- 啥? 多少钱? - 一百卢比
- What? How much? - 100 rupees.
对了  还附有一条留言
And yes, there's a message as well.
这儿
See.
" 瓦萨姆先生 我想亲自送还
" Waseem sir, I wanted to return it personally...
可是我无能为力
... but l am helpless.
你的血汗钱对我无用武之地
Your hard-earned money is no use to me.
你的昂儒 "
Yours, Ajju. "
这是你的吗?
It's yours, isn't it?
是的
Yes, it is.
谢谢
Thank you.
给你
Here you go.
- 我们快赶不上公交了 - 拉胡尔找你
- We were about to miss the bus... - Rahul's called.
- 拉胡尔 - 长官 我们找到他们的线索
- Yes, Rahul. - Sir, we've information about them.
几年前 大概3年前
Couple of years ago, maybe three years ago.
没有人会想到他会有精彩的表现
One would have never associated him with a shot like this.
但他总有一天在板球上
But l think he has come to learn and life..
学会敲门并且终会表现出色
..in one day cricket and has played some really good shots.
好球!
Shot!
六分!
Six!
他必须再来一次
Once more, he has to do it.
# 年轻之时 罪犯满街 #
In the youth, was on the streets. Half the world are sinners.
# 谁为始祖 全是跟风 #
Who is original, all is a copy.
# 混乱不堪 #
Whole life is hectic.
# 他的颈 他的腿 他的身段 她的面纱 #
His neck, his legs. His loin cloth, her veil.
# 他的手指 他的头发 拿着 干活去 #
His finger, his hair, hold it and get your work done.
# 别过于自信 #
Don't be over confident,
# 生命的真谛是抓住别放手 #
life is catch and hold.
# 抓住别放手 #
Catch and hold.
# 揪住小偷的辫子 意味着得到食物 #
Catch the thief by his tail. Everything is related to food.
# 无论是孟买 巴特那还是德里 #
Police and thieves, cat and mouse,
警察和小偷就像猫和老鼠 #
whether it is Mumbai, Patna or Delhi.
# 每一个人都在追逐 #
Everyone is playing catch.
# 但金钱却被牢牢掌握 #
But money has a good hold.
# 世界就像一个野兽 #
The world is an animal,
# 金钱则引导野兽的前进 #
money leads this animal.
# 无论是白人还是黑人 #
The money should come any how.
# 总有一天会富有 #
Whether white or black.
# 每个人都在追逐金钱 #
Everyone is running after this money.
# 有许多关于金钱的态度 #
There is a lot of attitude with this.
# 觉得金钱无趣 那追逐它吧 #
If its black then catch it.
# 抓住别放手 #
Catch and hold.
# 年轻人总为示爱而困扰 #
Youth is stuck in the yes or no of love.
# 如果她答应了 约她去看电影喝咖啡 #
If she says yes, then movie and coffee.
# 如果她拒绝 那就说" 妹妹 请原谅我" #
If she says no, then sister, forgive me.
# 地球在转 真爱长留 #
The world comes in between, but love continues.
# 不管你是否相信爱情 爱情永存 #
Whether you have sense or no, still it continues.
# 捕获某人的心吧 #
Catch the one on the way.
# 抓住别放手 #
Catch and hold.